[
    {
        "question":"How long did it take Conor McGregor to defeat Jose Aldo at UFC 194?",
        "options":["30 seconds","13 seconds","15 seconds","45 seconds"],
        "answer":"13 seconds"
    },
    {
        "question":"Who has the most wins in the UFC?",
        "options":["Jim Miller","Anderi Arlovski","Donald Cerrone","Neil Magny"],
        "answer":"Jim Miller"
    },
    {
        "question":"Who Has the Most Wins by Submission in the UFC?",
        "options":["Royce Graice","Demian Maia","Charles Oliveria","Gunnar Nelson"],
        "answer":"Charles Oliveria"
    },
    {
        "question":"Who has the fastest knockout in UFC history?",
        "options":["Don Frye","Leon Edwards","Duane Ludwig","Jorge Masvidal"],
        "answer":"Jorge Masvidal"
    },
    {
        "question":"Who was the first female fighter inducted into the UFC Hall of Fame?",
        "options":["Amanda Nunes","Miesha Tate","Holly Holm","Ronda Rousey"],
        "answer":"Ronda Rousey"
    },
    {
        "question":"Who was the first UFC Bantamweight Champion?",
        "options":["Dominick Cruz","Renan Barão","T.J. Dillashaw","Urijah Faber"],
        "answer":"Dominick Cruz"
    },
    {
        "question":"Who has the most knockouts in UFC history?",
        "options":["Chuck Liddell","Derrick Lewis","Matt Brown","Vitor Belfort"],
        "answer":"Derrick Lewis"
    },
    {
        "question":"Who holds the record for the most significant strikes landed in a UFC fight?",
        "options":["Nate Diaz", "Rob Font","Max Holloway","Jared Cannonier"],
        "answer":"Max Holloway"
    },
    {
        "question":"Who was the first UFC Strawweight champion?",
        "options":["Rose Namajunas","Joanna Jędrzejczyk","Carla Esparza","Jessica Andrade"],
        "answer":"Carla Esparza"
    },
    {
        "question":"Which of these fighters won both a UFC title and an Olympic gold medal?",
        "options":["Jose Aldo","Yoel Romero","Henry Cejudo","Daniel Cormier"],
        "answer":"Henry Cejudo"
    },
    {
        "question":"What former UFC champion was traded to ONE Championship for their welterweight champ?",
        "options":["Chuck Liddell","Matt Hughes","Tyron Woodley","Demetrious Johnson"],
        "answer":"Demetrious Johnson"
    },
    {
        "question":"What year was the UFC Founded?",
        "options":["November 1993","February 2005","January 1987","August 1996"],
        "answer":"November 1993"
    },
    {
        "question":"First fighter to hold two belts at the SAME TIME?",
        "options":["Randy Coture","Daniel Cormier","Anderson Silva","Conor Mcgregor"],
        "answer":"Conor Mcgregor"
    },
    {
        "question":" Which venue has held the most UFC events?",
        "options":["Madison Square Garden","T-Mobile Arena","MGM Grand","O2 Arena"],
        "answer":"MGM Grand"
    },
    {
        "question":"Which city was used as fight island during the covid-19 pandemic?",
        "options":["Vega","Dubai","Abu Dhabi","Mexico City"],
        "answer":"Abu Dhabi"
    },
    {
        "question":"Who has officiated the most UFC fights?",
        "options":["Herb Dean","Marc Goddard","Mario Yamasaki","Dan Miraglotta"],
        "answer":"Herb Dean"
    },
    {
        "question":"Which 2 fighters are the only people to get a 4th fight?",
        "options":["Moreno / Figueiredo","Coture / Liddell","Jones / Cormier", "Volkanovski / Holloway"],
        "answer":"Moreno / Figueiredo"
    },
    {
        "question":"Who was Khabibs last UFC fight against?",
        "options":["Dustin Poirier", "Edson Barboza", "Conor Mcgregor","Justin Gaethje"],
        "answer":"Justin Gaethje"
    },
    {
        "question":"What was the first Ufc event to feature weight classes?",
        "options":["UFC 4","UFC 5", "UFC 6", "UFC 7"],
        "answer":"UFC 7"
    },
    {
        "question":"Who holds the record for the most UFC title defenses?",
        "options":["Anderson Silva","Jon Jones","Demetrious Johnson","Georges St-Pierre"],
        "answer":"Demetrious Johnson"
    }
    
]